Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this section on reference types, we would discuss about what are reference types, how are they stored
在关于引用类型的这一节中，我们将讨论什么是引用类型，它们是如何存储在内存中的？
in memory, and how are they different from primitive types. In the previous sections,
在内存中存储，以及它们与原始类型有什么不同。在前面的章节中。
we created a number of classes and this is how we create instances, right.
我们创建了一些类，这就是我们创建实例的方法，对吗。
We used a new jupiter
我们使用了一个新的jupiter
here is a reference variable, Planet here is a reference type, and over here when we created a int variable,
这里是一个引用变量，Planet这里是一个引用类型，在这里，我们创建了一个int变量。
i is a primitive variable and int is a primitive type.
i是一个原始变量，int是一个原始类型。
We will discuss about all of these concepts and we will go one level deeper.
我们将讨论所有这些概念，我们将深入一个层次。
We will talk about how the reference variables and primitive variables are stored in memory,
我们将讨论参考变量和原始变量是如何存储在内存中的。
what happens behind these screens when you assign a value to a primitive variable or you try to assign
当你给一个原始变量赋值或试图给另一个原始变量赋值时，在这些屏幕后面会发生什么？
one value to another.
一个值到另一个值时，这些屏幕背后会发生什么。
We will also talk about how they are initialized.
我们还将谈论它们是如何被初始化的。
We will also look at a few reference types in Java.
我们还将看一下Java中的一些引用类型。
These are predefined in the sense that Java provides them for you.
这些是预定义的，即Java为你提供了它们。
So, they come free for you with Java.
因此，它们在Java中是免费的。
These are string.
这些是字符串。
There are a set of classes called wrapper classes and also we will look at a few date time stuff.
有一组类被称为包装类，我们还将看看一些日期时间的东西。
So, we'll look at LocalDate and LocalDateTime.
所以，我们会看一下LocalDate和LocalDateTime。
I'll see you in the first video where we would start discussing more about reference types and variables.
我们将在第一个视频中见，在那里我们将开始讨论更多关于引用类型和变量。
Until then, bye-bye
在那之前，拜拜